[{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975174475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":24427,"timeElapsed":109931},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975182761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8283,"timeElapsed":118217},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975191493,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":8728,"timeElapsed":126950},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975198658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":7161,"timeElapsed":134114},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975202576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3917,"timeElapsed":138033},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975206459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":3879,"timeElapsed":141915},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975209976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3514,"timeElapsed":145433},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975224261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":14279,"timeElapsed":159717},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975233061,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"6","question":"If you were able to live to the age of 90 and retain either the mind or body of a 30-year-old for the last 60 years of your life, which would you want?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8797,"timeElapsed":168518},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975247323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":12731,"timeElapsed":182780},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975253228,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":5902,"timeElapsed":188684},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975259189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":5960,"timeElapsed":194646},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975262693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3502,"timeElapsed":198150},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975267026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":4331,"timeElapsed":202483},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975270993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3963,"timeElapsed":206450},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975274127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3130,"timeElapsed":209584},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975280078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":5948,"timeElapsed":215535},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975285662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":5578,"timeElapsed":221119},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975295593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":8396,"timeElapsed":231050},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975299428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3831,"timeElapsed":234884},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975304577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5146,"timeElapsed":240034},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975308427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3846,"timeElapsed":243884},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975311994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3564,"timeElapsed":247451},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975321077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":9080,"timeElapsed":256534},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975324044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":2964,"timeElapsed":259501},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975329429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5381,"timeElapsed":264885},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975332877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3445,"timeElapsed":268334},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975348045,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":13632,"timeElapsed":283502},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975351411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3362,"timeElapsed":286867},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975357376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":5962,"timeElapsed":292833},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975361060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3682,"timeElapsed":296517},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975365743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4679,"timeElapsed":301199},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975369241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3496,"timeElapsed":304698},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975373941,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4698,"timeElapsed":309398},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975379340,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5398,"timeElapsed":314797},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975383327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"33","question":"Share a personal problem or something you have struggled with and any experiences you have had trying to address it.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3985,"timeElapsed":318784},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975389960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":5163,"timeElapsed":325417},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975393211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3248,"timeElapsed":328667},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975398844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5630,"timeElapsed":334301},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975410328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11480,"timeElapsed":345785},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975414062,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":3728,"timeElapsed":349519},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975416643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2577,"timeElapsed":352100},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975419344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2698,"timeElapsed":354801},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975426528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":7179,"timeElapsed":361984},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975431560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5029,"timeElapsed":367017},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975448127,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":15047,"timeElapsed":383584},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975451992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3862,"timeElapsed":387449},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975457427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5432,"timeElapsed":392884},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975460410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2981,"timeElapsed":395866},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975464258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3844,"timeElapsed":399715},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975469043,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4784,"timeElapsed":404500},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975474775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5728,"timeElapsed":410232},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975478162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3383,"timeElapsed":413618},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975486477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":8311,"timeElapsed":421934},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975493423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6943,"timeElapsed":428880},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975502677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":7480,"timeElapsed":438134},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975506776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":4096,"timeElapsed":442233},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975511244,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4464,"timeElapsed":446701},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975514661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":3414,"timeElapsed":450118},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975518043,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3379,"timeElapsed":453500},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975520974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2928,"timeElapsed":456431},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975523494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2516,"timeElapsed":458950},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975529579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6080,"timeElapsed":465035},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975532561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"162","question":"How often do you get your hair cut? Where do you go? Have you ever had a really bad haircut experience?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2978,"timeElapsed":468018},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975539946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5865,"timeElapsed":475402},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975543177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3226,"timeElapsed":478634},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975547545,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4362,"timeElapsed":483002},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975551878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4328,"timeElapsed":487335},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975555143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3262,"timeElapsed":490600},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975558109,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2963,"timeElapsed":493566},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975560775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2663,"timeElapsed":496231},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975564844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4067,"timeElapsed":500301},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975567479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2630,"timeElapsed":502936},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975578611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":9715,"timeElapsed":514067},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975581874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":3261,"timeElapsed":517331},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975585160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3286,"timeElapsed":520617},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975589657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4496,"timeElapsed":525114},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975596107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":6446,"timeElapsed":531564},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975599475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3367,"timeElapsed":534932},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975602893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3417,"timeElapsed":538350},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975611193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8296,"timeElapsed":546650},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975615794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4597,"timeElapsed":551251},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975620695,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4899,"timeElapsed":556152},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975632962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10880,"timeElapsed":568419},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975635345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2379,"timeElapsed":570802},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975639295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3947,"timeElapsed":574752},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975642076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2779,"timeElapsed":577532},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975645611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3534,"timeElapsed":581068},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975649161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3546,"timeElapsed":584618},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975652178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3014,"timeElapsed":587634},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975656860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":4679,"timeElapsed":592317},{"subjectID":"ucfpdk6ftl","prolificID":"666c76a1a7c9a36310fb4f56","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67699d794c6d679bdb390b7b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734975661358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4495,"timeElapsed":596815}]